Contact

sameer.ulhaq79@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sameer-ul-haq (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

.NET Framework Codelgniter PHP Native Android

Sameer UI Haq

Software Engineer at Naeem Impex

Pakistan

Summary

I'm passionate about my career to work for renowned organizations, and to make myself Asset for Organization.

Having Well-developed IT skills including Dot Net Framework (Web Applications and Web API) N-Tier Application, AJAX, JQuery and Deployment On Cloud (Microsoft Azure App Service and SQL Server), with Core Programming concepts OOP and Data Structures and Problem Solving Abilities. Had Worked On Many Live Project Updates while Working for Software houses, Also Developed an ERP for Textile Industry Single Handedly and its Deployment at Microsoft Azure.

Aim is to learn new technologies rather than sticking with one, Intrested in hybrid mobile application development if i get a chance working with it.

Experience

Naeem Impex Software Engineer October 2019 - Present (2 years 1 month) karachi

Development and Maintainance of ERP.

Mintbrains (Private) Limited
Junior Dotnet Developer
January 2019 - October 2019 (10 months)
Pakistan

Working on GroupM rebate system on Dot Net MVC With Entity Framework, LINQ Queries & AJAX requests. Also worked on small portals for dynamic websites on raw PHP.

OfficeAutomation
Internship
January 2018 - April 2018 (4 months)
Pakistan

Had worked on Dot Net Web App to deal with MYSQL Database through PHP API also for its native Android App and integration of API.

Repair and Maintainance of different projects, Dot Net.

Education

PAF-Karachi Institute of Economics & Technology Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (2016 - 2019)